

☐ SUMMARY

A software developer that loves to build things and working for continuous improvements. I do my best to contribute to a fun and engaging working environment. I enjoy technology and have experience with technologies like SQL/GraphQL and Python. A strong supporter of open source software and a diehard linux enthusiast.

MAGNUS LYNGRA

Software developer

■ WORK EXPERIENCE

2024-06 - present

Head Engineer

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway, Tromsø, NO

Working in a shared position between the education department and the IT department, trying to bring them closer together in relevant areas. This includes keeping a close dialogue between the two departments and furthering collaboration between them. I also assist in developing existing and new systems and solutions for the departments. This includes working with SQL, Python, GraphQL and other relevant technologies.

2022-03-2024-10

Head Engineer

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway, NO Company Description

- Advanced audio/video support
- Recording and streaming of lectures, courses and conferences
- Operation and management of audio/video equipment

2019-06-2022-03

Adviser

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway, Tromso, NO Admissions department

- Handling applications, writing SQL, interpreting law.
- 2016-02-2019-05

Higher Executive Officer

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway Company Description

- Guiding students and handling a variety of administrative tasks.
- 2014-01-2015-08

Secretary

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway, Tromso, NO

2014-09-2015-08

Consultant

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway

2015-08-2016-02

Veileder

NAV

Company Description

• Guiding users on their rights and opportunities through NAV

2012-03-2013-09

Salesman

Narvesen

2011-09-2012-06

Volunteer

Studenthuset Driv, Tromsø, NO

EDUCATION

2024-06

Bachelor's degree

The Arctic University of Norway

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway

Bachelor's degree with a major in Computer Science 08/2021 - 06/2024

2015-12

Master's Degree

The Arctic University of Norway

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway

Master's Degree, Political Science and Government 01/2013 - 12/2015

2013-12

Bachelor's degree

The Arctic University of Norway

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway

Bachelor's degree, Political Science and Government 01/2010 - 12/2013